A recent survey revealed
that people with cancer have a 20% chance of developing heart
disease, and the White House
estimates that there's a 20% chance
they'll develop a heart disease before turning seventeen.
Critical analysis clearly shows that
critical
illness insurance is a solution, and we all cover the
benefits. If there's any
particular side effect, you might have
seen it on our channel, and
videos are available on it. I'm reviewing different companies like Speak
Asia, Students, and Travelers. I'm reviewing
HDFC Ergo Insurance Plan for
Birthdays. So, basically, the
product provides you with a lump sum benefit,
which you can use for various medical
and treatment needs. You can use it
for various care and treatment purposes,
meaning
you get a lump sum benefit on top of hospitalization expenses, which you can
use for your post-surgery, career, post-diagnosis care.  You can do it,
suppose you deepen on the date and get
salvation, which you can pay from this,
your questions come that
after getting close, you can cover it from here,
you get the benefit of this, you
get the benefit in Sector-19,
you can also click on the income tax benefit
and the remaining balance to know what benefits this plant has
for you, so it is important to see
before clearing the planet video, for those who
I would like to use you, my
name is Dual Inko Chiku, I am so that I bring
videos for the heritage, so that
your personal life
becomes something else, because on our front side, this
cricket association is going on, you can move towards the video,
that is why you can
take the policy between 65 years of age, but you can take it for as long as you
want, if you
are less than 10 then get a
medical test done, you can take the policy,
after 90 you cannot do anything, there will be
no problem, it has soil in
listed glass sir, if you
know a little oil in particular race religion, then  You must be aware that
according to the list in this, if it is diagnosed, then
these forests of this land give leave, then the
holiday is listed glass, it is
on your screen, if there is any time in this, then
payment is made, nail polish
is available on the occasion, which you are understanding,
according to sources, milk is available, 2.5
lits maximum is available, ₹10 survival
period is 30 days, means there is some worry search
place, after times in it, fertile
soil is friendly, it will play now, the
waiting period of pre-existing digit
is four years, if there is any
placentries related to it, Kritika
Sengar problem will not be given for four years,
now let's talk about the premium,
I have taken it for the population, if you are taking a policy of ₹10 lakh
and the sharp thorn has fallen,
but you are taking a policy in 3135 years
and you are taking a policy of tailors, then
its premium is 720
sliding tax, 90 percent GST in it
This policy of these routes is being taken shift
in this group if you have this
player then the cream is 30
Meghna so because in the same manner
ghr ghr
k
computers and consolidated that those who are being killed regarding the
tiger, please
share in the comment section
our phone number email id cannot
see you in the next video a
reminder if you have not yet subscribed to the channel then
you get the subscription ok ji by vested on
[music]